# Abdinoor Suleman

## Senior Software Engineer

0634906862

xarwaashe00@gmail.com



https://www.dhaabooaysnc.ml/



Burao



graduated School of ICT have a warm and friendly demeanor always! Skilled at Web developer experience, Software developer, A+, N+ And have troubleshooting Computer problems and more than two years of ICT Specialist experience also developing more software's And Websites Successfully

#### **WORK EXPERIENCES**

### SOFTWARE Stack Developer

### Microwork's, Study/July 2018-May 2019

- ✓ Used Swift to develop a productivity app for iOS to help architects render and edit blueprints
- ✓ Worked with the development team to refine the debugging process
- Leveraged my knowledge of C#, Java and Python to write interfaces to manage backup log data

## Web Stack Developer

#### Study And test online servers / May 2018–August 2020

- ✓ Fixed 300+ bugs on the website and implemented numerous enhancements to improve the overall user experience
- Used HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to contribute to a full revamp of the flagship app's homepage, leading to a 16% increase in click rates
- Maintained and regularly updated webpages on WordPress
- Assisted in developing a widget to help cyclists locate the nearest bike lane, which is now one of Spinor's most popular products

### **SKILLS**

#### **Technical**

JavaScript/Angular/React/Vue

Python/Ruby/PHP

Node.js/ASP.NET

PostgreSQL/MySQL

Object-oriented design

#### **Professional**

Effective communication

Team player

Strong problem solver

good time management

## **EDUCATION**

#### **B.S. / SCHOOL OF ICT**

For Gollis University

2017 - 2020

## **LANGUAGES**

English (Native)

Arabic (Native)

Somali (Professional)

## **INTERESTS**

Technology

Climbing & Hiking

Travelling

